

MARTIN POSNIAK

BACHELOR OF MARKETING

ABOUT

After several years of experience in sales and marketing, in the middle of 2022 I discovered the world of programming, which I liked so much, that I made the decision to start training, with the aim of getting my first job as a Frontend developer.

CONTACT

+ 54 9 11 5339-2228



martin.posniak@hotmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/martin-posniak-272249a0/



Palermo, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

EDUCATION

UCES (Universidad de Ciencias Empresariales y Sociales)

Bachelor's degree in marketing, Apr 2010 - Dec 2016

UCA (Universidad Católica Argentina)

Digital Marketing Executive Program, May 2016 - Jul 2016

ORT High School

Technical bachelor with orientation in administrative management, Mar 2005 - Dec 2009

LANGUAGES

• ENGLISH: Oral and written training, advanced. Elementary School, High School and private lessons.

EXPERIENCE

Business Advisor

Grupo Mitre, Sep 2022 - Present

- Customer service and preparation of budgets.
- · Post-sale monitoring and prospecting.
- Trainer and supervisor of new salesmen.
- · Weekly team meetings and monthly sales review.

Real Estate Agent

RE/MAX Vanguard, Nov 2019 - Sep 2022

- · Weekly meetings with clients, post-sale follow-up and prospecting.
- Presentation of comparative market analysis and preparation of budget. Show of properties and negotiation with clients.
- · Assembly of promotional actions.
- · Constant training and monthly team meetings.

COURSES

Coder House

Backend Programming, Apr 2023 - Sep 2023

• JAVASCRIPT, SQL, NoSQL, NODE JS, MONGO DB, AJAX.

React JS, Feb 2023 - Apr 2023

• REACT, VITE, NODE-JS, REACT-BOOTSTRAP, CHAKRA UI

JavaScript, Nov 2022 - Jan 2023

• JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP, SWEETALERT2.

Web Development, Sep2022 - Nov 2022

• HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, SASS, GIT, GITHUB.